GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING
On Sunday, July 6, 1997 Prophet T.B. Joshua spoke forth a prophetic message,
stating that a star, a popular person, would die.
These were his words.
Amen!
A star will fall.
By next Sunday, I will tell you the length of days.
Let us keep our fingers crossed.
One popular person will die.
There is nothing we can do about it.
I know that star. I know what will happen, and I know the day and time it will happen.
On Sunday, July 13, 1997 Prophet T.B. Joshua spoke further on this prophetic message,
stating that the popular person was a woman and that she would pass away in an overseas country.
These were his words.
A popular person, a woman, will pass away in an overseas country.
I know where and I know the person.
People will condemn her because of what led to her death.
People will not like to hear it.
On Sunday, July 27, 1997 Prophet T.B. Joshua spoke a final time
regarding the popular woman who would die in an overseas country.
He then specifically stated her name.
These were his words.
Three weeks ago - I want to remind you. This is an international issue.
Many of us were here when I asked people to pray - that, a star will fall,
a great star that will shake the whole world.
And it will come to pass.
And I told you she's a very young person.
The whole world will shake.
Is it Diana?
I will be here with you people. You will learn of what happened.
It's a disaster. It is not something that --
In the early hours of the morning, Sunday, August 31, 1997, news broke out around the world
that Diana, Princess of Wales, had just died.
BBC
This is BBC Television from London.
Normal programming has been suspended.
Diana, Princess of Wales, has been seriously injured.
They had been enjoying dinner at the Ritz hotel.
Diana, the Princess of Wales, has, in fact, been killed.
Diana, Princess of Wales, has died.
The world has lost Princess Diana, age 36.
CNN Breaking News
This is CNN Breaking News.
I'm Jim Clancy at the CNN Center.
36-year-old Princess Diana and 42-year-old Dodi Al-Fayed, along with their driver,
were killed in the early morning hours in Paris
after apparently being chased at high speed by photographers on motorcycles.
Princess Diana was taken to a hospital where doctors tried to save her life.
They were unable to do that.
She died just about 1 1/2 hours ago.
It was announced that she died 2 hours earlier than that.
Apparently word was held as the sad news was passed on to (the family).
Prince Charles was staying with Prince William, the heir to the throne, and Prince Harry.
He is only 12 years old.
Prince William being 14 years of age.
This is the car in which they were riding.
It is a Mercedes Benz; it was a large vehicle.
It hit a concrete pillar at top speed at the Alma Bridge in Paris, along the Seine river.
It became clear that Princess Diana and Prince Charles were growing apart.
The newspapers would measure the days they spent separated.
A book "Diana: A True Story" by Andrew Morton revealed details of her unhappiness.
She had developed eating disorders and was even reported to have attempted suicide.
Eventually but out of the blue, the then-British Prime Minister John Major announced
that Diana and Charles would separate.
The British monarchy had not faced such a crisis since the abdication of King Edward VIII in 1936.
But the Princess was not to be deterred from maintaining her high public profile.
Once the couple's divorce was confirmed and freed from the shackles of royal protocol,
she began to be seen in public with other men.
She focused her official life on several charities -
as varied as the Royal Ballet in London and the Red Cross campaign against landmines.
Within the past few months, she had been in Angola and Bosnia
to see at first hand the effect of landmines
as a guest of the International Red Cross -
a stand that caused political controversy.
She managed to combine her charitable work with a high-profile social calendar.
But it was her liason with Dodi Al-Fayed
that had seemed to be the most serious since the breakup of her marriage.
Princess Diana 1961 - 1997